const film = [
    {
        number: "1",
        question: "How many James Bond films have there been?",
        answer: "26",
        hint: "There have been 24 official films"
    },
    {
        number: "2",
        question: "When was Monty Python's Life of Brian released?",
        answer: "1979",
        hint: "This is the year John Wayne died"
    },
    {
        number: "3",
        question: "In which two British cities is Trainspotting set?",
        answer: "edinburgh and london",
        hint: "The first is known as Auld Reekie and the second is capitol of England "
    },
    {
        number: "4",
        question: "Who directed the film Trainspotting?",
        answer: "danny boyle",
        hint: "More recent works include Slumdog millionaire and 127 hours"
    },
    {
        number: "5",
        question: "Who played King George VI in The King's Speech?",
        answer: "colin firth",
        hint: "Born in GrayShott 10th September 1960"
    },
    {
        number: "6",
        question: "How many Bridget Jones films are there?",
        answer: "3",
        hint: "Between 2 and 5"
    },
    {
        number: "7",
        question: "And who plays the iconic Bridget?",
        answer: "renee zellweger",
        hint: "Born in Texas 25th April 1969"
    },
    {
        number: "8",
        question: "Name the actor who played Harry Potter?",
        answer: "danial radcliffe",
        hint: "Born London 23rd July 1989"
    },
    {
        number: "9",
        question: "Name the actor who played Professor McGonagall?",
        answer: "maggie smith",
        hint: "More recent works include Downton Abbey"
    },
    {
        number: "10",
        question: "Stanley Kubrick's 1971 version of 'A Clockwork Orange' is a British cult classic. But who wrote the novel?",
        answer: "anthony burgess",
        hint: "Born Manchester 25th February 1917"
    },
    {
        number: "11",
        question: "Which airport is the opening scene of Love Actually set in?",
        answer: "Heathrow",
        hint: "An airport located in London"
    },
    {
        number: "12",
        question: "Name the actor who played Django in the film Django unchained?",
        answer: "jamie foxx",
        hint: "Real name Eric Marlon Bishop"
    },
    {
        number: "13",
        question: "Withnail and I is a 1987 British comedy written and directed by Bruce Robinson. But where in London do Withnail and I live?",
        answer: "camden town",
        hint: "Famed for its market and fashion warren"
    },
    {
        number: "14",
        question: "Julia Roberts stars in the iconic rom-com Notting Hill. But what are the occupations of the character she plays?",
        answer: "actress",
        hint: "The same job she has outside of the film"
    },
    {
        number: "15",
        question: "What type of dance is the 2000 film Billy Elliot about?",
        answer: "ballet",
        hint: "The type of dance originated during the Italian Renaissance"
    },
    {
        number: "16",
        question: "Who played Carrie in Four Weddings and a Funeral?",
        answer: "andy macdowell",
        hint: "Born South Carolina 21st April 1958"
    },
    {
        number: "17",
        question: "The famous adaptation of Price & Prejudice starring Keira Knightly was released in what year?",
        answer: "2005",
        hint: "Between 2003 and 2007"
    },
    {
        number: "18",
        question: "This is England (2006) was directed by who?",
        answer: "shane meadows",
        hint: "Also known for directing Dead Man's Shoes"
    },
    {
        number: "19",
        question: "Who played The Queen in the 2006 film about Her Royal Majesty?",
        answer: "helen mirren",
        hint: "Born London 26th July 1945"
    },
    {
        number: "20",
        question: "Who directed the 2009 adaptation of Sherlock Holmes?",
        answer: "Two and a half",
        hint: "Also known for hit movies like Snatch and Lock, Stock and Two Smoking Barrels"
    }

];

export default film;